本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：石头  大红包  小花豆  木浅薰
翻译：卫老哥  姚小事儿  MythCreator
翻译：吃货丁小七  feilixiaozi  王小麦
时间轴：包  kitty  凭陵新月
校对：王小麦
后期：8T   MythCreator     总监：王小麦
《真探》前情提要
你觉得是怎么回事
What is it you think happened?
有人杀了这个女孩  用她的尸体大做文章
Someone killed this girl, made a big show of it...
在你们的一间旧教堂上
left a painting of the crime scene
留下了一幅犯罪现场的画
on one of your old churches.
你太沉迷了
You're obsessive.
你也沉迷
You're obsessive, too,
只不过不是沉迷工作
just not about the job.
所以你要跟那个人回家吗
So are you gonna go home with this guy?
这真的不关你事
It's really none of your business.
住手
Stop!
你知道这是真的吗
You know if it's true?
我什么都没听说
I didn't hear anything,
你一直都在干什么  小马
What have you been doing, Marty?
我找到了另一个女孩
I found another girl.
她服用了冰毒和迷幻剂
She was positive for meth and LSD.
你有没有想过
You ever think maybe
他可能是想把事情往他希望的方向推动呢
he tried to push things where he wanted them to go?
我们这案子有线索了  头儿
Hey, we caught a break in the case, boss.
我以为你们已经不管那个案子了
I thought you were handing that off.
她有男朋友吗
She had a boyfriend you know about,
雷金  雷金·勒杜
Reggie. Reggie Ledoux
雷金·勒杜8个月前逃离了假释
Reggie Ledoux skipped parole 8 months ago.
再次被捕  这次和一个毒品实验室有关
He's busted in connection to a narcotics lab
它们制造冰毒和迷幻药
used to make meth and LSD,
勒杜在阿沃伊斯蹲了两年
Ledoux did two years at Avoyelles,
猜猜他最后四个月的室友是谁
and guess who his cellmate was the last 4 months.
查理·兰
Charlie Lange.
我知道我在做什么
I know what I do.
对  确实
No, you did.
我要发一份通缉令  对象是雷金纳德·勒杜
I need an all-state APB on one Reginald Ledoux.
真探
第一季第四集
你们要干嘛
What you doing?
你敢耍我们  查理
You fucked with us, Charlie.
我没有啊  警官
I did not, sir.
雷金·勒杜
Reggie Ledoux.
我压根不想认识那怪咖
Hey, I don't even want to know that freak, man.
你们也没问过关于雷金的事
Y'all ain't asked nothin' about Reggie.
我操  伙计  我老婆刚死
Fuck, man, my-- my wife just died--
是前妻
Ex-wife!
你让雷金·勒杜杀了她  是不是
You had Reggie Ledoux take her out, didn't you?
没有
No.
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about, man?
雷金  把她杀了还插上鹿角  我...
Reggie? Put her out there with them antlers on? I--
你让雷金干的吗
You have Reggie do it?
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
雷金·勒杜干的吗
Reggie Ledoux did this?
雷金·勒杜
Reggie Ledoux?
操他娘的  雷金·勒杜干的吗
Reggie motherfuckin' Ledoux did this?!
我操  放我出去
Fuck, man! Shit! Let me out, man!
放我出去  妈的
Let me out! Fuck, man!
查理
Hey, Charlie?
你演得再好  我们也不会给你发奖的
We're not gonna give you the Oscar no matter how hard you try.
去你妈的  你都不了解我
Oh, fuck you, man. You don't know me.
你都不了解我经历过什么
You don't know what I been through.
你们在说什么  跟我讲清楚
And what are you talking about? You talk to me!
勒杜知道她的情况  对吗
Ledoux knew about her, right?
你跟他提过她吗
You talk about her to him?
没错  男人在一起不就聊这些
Yeah, man--yeah, the way you do sharing a house.
操过的女人上过的妞儿
Yeah, you talk pussy, talk scores.
不都这样吗
That's what you do.
给他看过她的照片  对吗
Showed him pictures of her, hmm?
是啊  可能给他看过
Yeah, I guess so, yeah.
我第一次入狱的时候她给了我几张照片
I had some she give me when I first went down,
让我没事可以看看
stuff for me to look at.
好像是宝丽来照片吧
You know, like polaroids.
他是个大块头
He was a big guy--
比你块头大多了
a lot bigger than you.
你是说你们关系不好吗
Do you tell me you didn't get along?
不  大部分时候  关系挺好的
Nah, I mean, I did, most part.
必须得好好相处  同住一个屋檐啊
You've got to, you're sharing a house,
就像我刚说的
like I'm saying.
我是说  他可以让你嗨起来
I mean, he gets you high, man,
但他是个怪胎  我压根不想认识他
but he's creep. I ain't want to know him.
跟我说说勒杜的事
Tell me about Ledoux.
怎么怪胎了
How is he creep?
他是个厨子  像个化学家一样
He's a cook, you know, like a chemist?
他能用厨房里的东西搞出花样
He used to, uh, make shit out of kitchen stuff--
煮煮清洁剂之类乱七八糟的东西
cook down cleansers and whatnot.
用土豆皮和炸东西的油做高挥发性酸浆
Used tater skins and fry grease to make high-test sour mash.
他很懂这些东西  但是  怎么说呢
He got mad knowledge for that shit, but, like, I don't know, man,
他说话的时候像个恋童癖似的
he talk like a short-eyes, like something.
你什么意思  他不会在这里说那些吧
How you mean? He wouldn't talk that shit up in here.
不  伙计  他没有
No, man, he didn't.
只是有时候  我和他到了晚上
Like, me and him at night,
用他做的那些东西爽翻天
blasted up on one of his mixes.
他做的有些玩意儿
I mean, he could brew some shit up
能搞得你腾云驾雾
put you up out your head, man.
在这里头可太牛逼了
That's a big deal in here.
操他妈的  出去了也牛逼
I mean, fuck, man, it's a big deal out there, too.
他说了些什么乱七八糟的
So, uh, what kind of shit was he talking?
他说在这儿往南有个地方
He said that there's this place down south
有钱人都去那里  搞邪恶的仪式
where all these rich men go to, uh, devil-worship.
他说...
He said that, uh...
他们  他们用孩子之类的作祭品
They-- they sacrifice kids and whatnot.
女人和孩子们都被...
Women and children all got--
都在那儿被杀  还有...
all got murdered there, and, um,
一些关于一个叫卡寇莎的地方的事情
something about someplace called Carcosa
以及黄袍国王
and the yellow king.
他说在树林里好像有个古老的石头阵
He said there's all these, like, old stones out in the woods,
人们去那里朝拜
people go to, like, worship.
他说...
He said, uh...
他说有很多正义的杀戮发生在那里
He said there's just so much good killin' down there.
雷金背上有个烙印
Reggie got this brand on his back,
像个螺纹
like in a spiral?
他说这是他们的标志
He says that's their sign.
这他妈的  你们懂了吗
What the fuck ever, you understand?
我不想听这家伙说话的  可他是个大个子
I don't listen to the man, but he's big,
所以我也不能叫他闭嘴
so I don't tell him to shut the fuck up, neither!
你记得他说起过什么朋友吗
You remember any buddies he ever talked about?
我们查过这里的记录
So we checked the records here,
从没人来看过他
and he hadn't ever had any visitors.
我们都认识泰龙·威姆斯
We both know Tyrone Weems.
泰龙或许会告诉你们他在哪
Tyrone like to tell you where he's at.
伙计  雷金是个货真价实的疯子
Look, man, Reggie's crazy, like, for real.
跟一个整天在你耳边
Had to be tough,
胡言乱语的疯子一起住
living with somebody spouting insane shit
日子肯定不好过
in your ear all day long.
我告诉了你们那么多  你们不给我点回报吗
You gonna give me something for what I told you just now?
给你假释
Parole Board nod.
公平合理
Fair's fair.
你们觉得因为我跟他提起过朵拉...
You think 'cause I talked to him about Dori that...
所以是我害死了她吗
I might have got her killed?
你脱不了干系
You probably had something to do with it.
我觉得你不该给他看那些照片的
I don't think you should have shown him those pictures.
你觉得呢
Do you?
我们得找到这个泰龙·威姆斯
We need to find this Tyrone Weems,
看看他知道些关于勒杜的什么事
see what he knows about Ledoux.
是的
Yeah.
阿布维尔市警察局
犯罪记录报告
姓名: 雷金·勒杜
社保号: 921-88-82732
出生地: 路易斯安那州
人种: 白人
性别: 男
身高: 2米
体重: 102公斤
发色: 金色
瞳孔色: 淡褐色
有无疤痕: 有
有无纹身: 有
出生日期: 1960年11月13日
你不必告诉他这是他的错
You didn't have to tell him it was his fault.
这家伙已经够惨的了
Guy was already low.
是啊  他先关心自己
Yeah, he asked about his end first.
假释委员会的态度
Parole Board.
所以呢
So?
去他的
So fuck him.
你真搞笑  小马
You're funny, Marty--
对这个烂人起了恻隐之心
The shit you get soft about.
我想找到那个家族的所有能找到的人
I wanted every member of that family that I could find.
结果...
Turns out...
一个人都没找到
There weren't any.
你知道这情况在路易斯安那州有多奇怪吗
You know how weird that is in Louisiana?
他的一个表亲  德沃尔
A cousin, what was it, DeWall, was
除了一张卡车司机驾照之外没有任何档案资料
not on paper except for a, uh, trucker's license.
勒杜自从那次在假释期间逃掉之后
Ledoux had turned into a ghost
就人间蒸发了
from the time he skipped Parole check.
说说看  小伙子们
Tell me, young studs,
当你们碰到这种事的时候会怎么做
what would you do when you hit a wall like that?
我对这个指控的回应是  我走到那所屋子
Responding to the complaint, I approached the house.
看到纱门被打坏了而大门
Seeing that the screen door was broken and the inner door...
半开着  我觉得我的进入方式
ajar, I--I felt that entrance
遵守了标准程序
Complied with standard procedure.
进入屋内后
Upon entering the domicile,
我在茶几上发现了大麻
I noticed what appeared to be marijuana and a white powder
和一种白色粉末
on the coffee table.
马丁
Hey, Martin.
我们没什么好谈的  丽莎
We don't have to talk, Lisa.
你休想逃避
The hell we don't.
你上周不该那么对我
You don't get to do what you did to me last week.
对不起  我那天心里难受而且喝多了
Look, I'm sorry. I was hurt and real drunk.
现在跟我说说
Talk to me now.
好吧  祝你生活顺利
Ok. Ah, I wish you a great life
并且祝你和你的新朋友好运
and good luck with your new friend.
你这个玩弄女性的混蛋
You philandering fucking asshole.
听着
Hey, look.
别在这儿大吵大闹的  行吗
There is no pageant to perform, ok,
你的失望跟我毫不相干
and your disappointment is irrelevant.
你没必要像那天那样  小马
You don't get to act like that, Marty,
或者像现在这样
or like this.
事实就是我很高兴知道你们俩在一起了
The fact is it's nice to know you got him,
而且我不想跟你谈论这些
and I don't want to have this conversation with you.
你必须要尊重我  小马
You need to respect me, Marty.
这就已经是尊重了
This is respect.
拉斯特找到了和以前一起谋杀案的联系
Rust figured a connection with an earlier death,
死者怀疑是莉安·奥利弗
suspicious-- Rianne Olivier.
引我们查到了死者的
Led us to the DB's
前男友雷金纳德·勒杜  35岁
old boyfriend, Reginald Ledoux, 35.
姓名: 雷金纳德·勒杜
社保号: 921-88-82732
出生地: 路易斯安那州
人种: 白人
性别: 男
身高: 2米
体重: 102公斤
被指控强奸了一位12岁的女孩
Statch rape charge against a 12-year-old,
因为缺乏证词而被无罪释放
Acquitted for lack of testimony.
曾经制过冰毒和摇头丸
Did a bit for manufacturing meth and lsd,
跟莉安的毒理检验相符合
which fits the tox screen for Lange.
他的老狱友就是莉安的前夫
His old cellmate was Lange's ex-husband.
他向他展示了一些她的艳照
He showed him some cheesecake pictures of her.
从我们对他的了解
Uh, from what we know about him,
和他说话的方式来看
the way he talked,
他听起来很在行
he sounds like he's real good for it.
没有任何关于他的人的消息
No line on any of his people.
陷入困境  只好另找突破口
Swamp folk, dug in off the grid.
我们在找他的重要客户  泰龙·威姆斯
We are tracking a ka, Tyrone Weems.
我们分发的资料里有他
He's in the sheets that we passed out.
有什么问题吗
Any questions?
我觉得没有  开始工作吧
I didn't think so. Let's get to work.
你是特丽萨·威姆斯
Are you Theresa Weems,
泰龙·威姆斯的母亲吗
Tyrone Weems' mom?
我有段时间没见着泰龙了
Tyrone ain't been around in a while.
好几个月了
You know, a few months.
我们吵架了  因为他把我的微波炉给卖了
We got in a fight 'cause he sold my microwave.
那他的朋友呢
And what about his friends?
你知道他们都去哪儿混
You know where they hang out?
我不知道  他和一个叫凯尔西的女孩
I don't know, he dated this girl Kelsey
谈过一段时间的恋爱
for a little while.
凯尔西  你最后一次见泰龙是什么时候
Kelsey, when's the last time you saw Tyrone?
几个月前了  我们分手了
Months. We've been broke up.
我再没他的消息  我也不想听到
I don't ever hear from him. I don't want to.
我听说他把肖达·米勒搞大肚子了
I heard he got Shawnda Miller pregnant.
所以你有他的地址和电话号码吗
So do you have his address, phone number?
听着  我真的很想帮忙  但我无能为力
Look. I really wish I could help you, but I can't.
我要回去工作了
I have to get back to work.
你认识那个女孩吗
You know that gal back there?
她有对象吗  经纪人呢
She got a man, manager?
非得要我亮出警徽吗
Hey, do I got to pull my badge?
我们这里可是合法经营
Hey, we run clean here.
当你因为大陪审团的调查而关门六个月
How you gonna run when you're shut down
到时候你准备怎么经营呢
6 months for a grand jury inquiry?
你为什么要逼我说这些呢
Why are you making me say this shit, man?
你认识她以前的男人吗
Do you know her old man?
认识  他会过来接她
Yeah, he came around, collecting from her.
老板把他踢出去了
Boss kicked him out
因为他想把一个叫克里斯蒂的女孩给卖了
for trying to sell Christie, the girls.
那是一个月之前的事了
That was about a month ago.
看起来眼熟吗
Look familiar?
-对  就是他  -他还有接过她吗
- Yeah, that's him. - He ever pick her up?
有的
Yeah.
继续调查泰龙·威姆斯
Went to work on Tyro Weems,
了解他的同事和家人
known associates, family.
既然我们已经有嫌疑人了
Had a little leeway with Quesada
在柯萨达那里就有了回旋余地
now that we had our suspect.
他妈的
Fuck!
他妈的  他妈的  该死的
Fuck! Fuck! Goddamn it!
-丽莎  -感觉如何
- Lisa? - How does it feel?
我跟你说过了你不能这样对人
I told you you can't treat people like this.
听着  我只需要知道
Listen, I just need to know
你到底跟她说了些什么
exactly what you told her.
你觉得你那样做没事吗
You think it's ok what you do?
你们这些男人都觉得你们这样对妻子
All of you think it's ok to treat your wives
是没事的  这样对女人
the way you do, to treat women the way--
该死的骗子流氓  这就是你的下场
Fucking liars and bullies, and this is what you get!
这就是你的下场
This is what you get!
我是有孩子的
I have children.
你毁了我的生活
You blew up my life,
你他妈个臭婊子
You fucking whore!
你刚才骂我什么了
What did you just call me?!
What did you just call me,
你娘了个臭逼的贱屌  他娘的吃屎的贱货
you fucking wet-noodle, whiskey-dick faggot fuck?!
我干死你  你个贱人
I will skull-fuck you, you bitch!
喂  杰克吗
Hello, Jake?
-杰克  是你吗  -小马
- Jake, is this you? - Marty?
-玛姬在吗  -跟你半毛钱关系都没有
- Is Maggie there? - That's none of your goddamn business.
杰克  我知道她在那儿
Jake, I know she's there,
我知道她在那儿  你就让她接电话吧
I know she's there, so just put her on the phone,
可以吗  求你了
would you, please?
离她远点  你他妈混蛋
Leave her alone, you fuckin' asshole.
-杰克  我  -你没听清楚我说的
- Jake, I-- - you're not hearing me.
-我不知道她怎么说的  -别来烦她
- I don't know what she told you. - Leave her alone.
我也知道我们一向不合
And I know we haven't always seen eye to eye--
-没错  我们确实合不来  -求你
- You're goddamn right, we haven't seen eye to eye. - Just please,
-让她接下电话就行  求你  -不行
- Put her on the phone for me. Just please -- - no, no.
你就是个混蛋  小马
You are no damn good, Marty,
你配不上她  别再给她打电话了
She deserves better, and don't call here again.
杰克
Jake.
你们有过多少前妻
How many exes you guys have?
我就是这个意思
I mean, that's what I'm talking about.
我做错了吗
Did I make some mistakes?
那毋庸置疑
Yes.
你知道那个关于侦探的诅咒吗
You know the detective's curse?
答案就在眼前
Solution was right under my nose,
可却注定专注于错的线索
but I was paying attention to the wrong clues?
-待会见  -再见
- See you later. - Bye, hon.
妈的
Damn it.
操
Fuck.
雷金·勒杜在哪  快说
Reggie Ledoux. Where is he? Now.
要问这个你直接问嘛  至于动手吗
That's what this is about? Yo, man, why didn't you say so?
他在哪儿
Where the fuck is he?
听说他还在制毒
I--I heard he still cook.
听说他出狱后就不再卖货了
I heard he stopped selling after he did his bit,
他现在只为一个客户干
that he only cook for one client now.
为谁
Who?
某个摩托车党
Some bike gang.
他们定了他所有的货  而且是大宗订单
They buy all his product. Bulk order, no mess.
从俱乐部听来的  没了
I heard this at the clubs is all.
所以雷金也不再卖散货了
Reggie don't distribute no more.
哪个摩托车党
Which bike club?
钢铁英雄还是什么的
Iron Heroes or some shit.
钢铁十字军
Iron-Iron Crusaders.
就这么个怪名字  我也不懂他们的想法
I don't keep up with them gearheads.
钢铁十字军  你确定
Iron Crusaders? You sure?
没错
Yup. Them ones.
我就听说他们的货都是雷金弄的
What I heard, Reggie cook their loads and that's all.
闭上眼睛数一百
Close your eyes and count to a hundred,
谢谢合作
if you can.
开始
Go.
1... 2...
-大点声  -3
- Louder. - 3!
4... 5...
我跟威姆斯谈了
Listen I-I talked to Weems and, uh,
雷金在为德克萨斯的什么摩托车党干活
the dude is cooking for some motorcycle gang out of texas.
帮派叫钢铁十字军
Iron Crusaders.
什么  钢铁十字军
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, but--Iron--Iron Crusaders?
你确定名字没错吗
You're sure he said Iron Crusaders?
我确定
I'm sure he said Iron Crusaders.
那我们
So we'll, uh,
明天去追查这个帮派的下落吧
We'll chase that tomorrow, yeah?
-你现在在哪  -我在忙
- What are you doing right now? - Right now I'm busy.
我当时
And, as I recall, I...
总得抽时间
I had to take some personal time,
看望父亲
see my dad.
那都是  17年前的事了
I mean, this is like, what, 17 years ago?
你们得理解
I mean, you'll have to understand
人到中年记忆力会有所减退
if my memory hasn't sharpened in the interim.
-弗兰  电话交给你了  -好的
- Fran, stay by the phone. - I will.
玛姬  我能跟你谈谈吗
Maggie, can I talk to you for just a second?
没时间  今天我夜班
No. I'm working graveyard.
女儿们在我爸妈那
Girls are with my mom and dad.
留言上都告诉你了  小马
It's all in the note, Marty.
能不能给我个解释的机会
Ok, will you give me a chance to--
她直接来了家里
She came to my home.
当着女儿的面  你这个谎话连篇的混蛋
Our daughters saw her. You lying fuck.
愚蠢可恶
You stupid, lying fuck.
看在上帝份上  听我说  玛姬
Jesus christ. Listen to me, Mags.
我那天晚上的话都是真心的
I meant everything I said the other night, every word.
-我真的不再那样了  -拜托
- I-I stopped. - Oh, my god.
你觉得你不再出轨这事就算了吗
You think your betrayal's removed by its interruption?
她简直令人作呕  你也是
She was disgusting. You're disgusting.
-你没法弥补  -听我说
- You can't fix this. - Listen to me. God, listen--
-放开我  -好的
- Get your hands off me. - Ok.
我当时  只是心乱
I-I've been -- I've been a mess.
不知所措了
Rattled. My...
因为  我父亲的离世
Just... My dad dying--
拜托  他都死了一年了
Oh, my god. That was a year ago.
还有酗酒什么的
And drinking and--
我不在乎你的感受了
I don't give a shit about your goddamn feelings.
别再干涉我和女儿们的生活了  小马
You need to get out of our lives, Marty, me and the girls'.
留言都写的很清楚了
Read the note. It's all there
-不许你再来我家  -我不信你忍心
- and you can't come home. - You don't mean that.
-你不是认真的  -我是认真的
- You don't mean that. - Yes. Yes, I do
听着  我
Listen, I...
我不会让你破坏掉我的家庭的
You are not gonna break up my fuckin' family, ok?
-滚出去  -我不要
- Get out of here right now! - No.
打搅一下  你没事吧  玛姬
Excuse me. You all right, Maggie?
先生  我建议你离开
Sir, I suggest you leave.
没事  大夫  我是州警
Everything's fine, doc. I'm state police.
很好  但你现在是以此身份而来吗
I appreciate that, but are you here in that capacity now,
作为执法人员
as--as law enforcement?
你们给我住手
You don't want to do this.
把你们的手拿开  妈的
Get your hands off me, goddamn it,
把你们管事的叫来
and call your commanding officer.
-你丢人丢够了  小马  -放屁
- You're making a scene, Marty! - No!
现在还没人丢人  除非这些商场保安想丢人
There is no scene, unless mall patrol here makes one.
我在冷静的跟我妻子讨论私人问题
I am calmly discussing a private matter with my wife!
讨论方式有点太醒目了  放松
Private in a pretty public way, man. Easy, easy.
-这儿跟你没他妈任何关系  -是的
- This is none of your fuckin' business. - No, no.
跟我没关系  但我们有事要做
It's none of my business, but we got to work.
听到了吗  小马
You hear me, Marty?
我有一条关于勒杜的线索
I got a line on Ledoux.
我他妈刚弄到
I got it right fuckin' now.
我要你一起来  暂时放下这边的烂摊子
I need you to come in, leave this shit till later.
我爱你  宝贝
I love you, honey,
我不会放弃的
and I ain't givin' up.
走吧
Come on.
我们可以找到勒杜  小马  但是会不好收拾
We can get to Ledoux. Marty, it's gonna be dirty.
我只想要她再给我一次机会
I just need her to give me another shot.
我要是能再有一次机会
If I could just get another shot--
我跟你说个事吧
Listen, can I tell you something?
好
Yeah.
这跟我没关系
This is none of my business.
我不想听
I don't want to hear it.
好吧  抱歉
All right. I'm sorry.
你这个混蛋
You total shit.
你知道吗  你也有责任
You know, this is part on you, you know?
是你就这么插进我的生活
You can't just slide into my life,
制造紧张关系  对我指手画脚
creating tensions, judging me--
怎么  是我让你去搞年轻版玛姬的吗
What, I make you tap some bimbo, looks like a young Maggie?
是我让你到处炫耀这事的吗
I make you flaunt that shit?
操  那晚在长角酒吧
Fuck, that night at the Longhorn,
你那么明目张胆盯着她看
you were so obvious, man, checking her out,
而她会跟踪你过去就已经够疯得了
and she looked crazy enough to have followed you there.
你吹那么多牛逼  还不知道疯逼什么样吗
With all the dick swagger you roll, you can't spot crazy pussy?
是我搞砸了
I fucked up.
我只是
I just...
我喜欢狂野的东西  一直都是
I like something wild. I always did.
我只是  感觉就像
I just... It feels like it--
抚平了我生活的其他部分
It smoothes out the other parts of my life most of--
小马  我再说一次  这他妈跟我没关系
Listen, Marty, one more time. It's none of my fuckin' business.
我操
Ah, fuck.
听着  我们有活儿要干
Look, we got a job to do.
私下干  我只能想到这法子
Off-book. That's the only play I can think of.
我得把家里的事情搞定
I--I got to straighten out things with the family.
我得处理好
I got to fix it.
那个摩托车党  我认识他们
That bike club. I know 'em.
我做缉毒警的时候跟他们打过交道
I had deals with 'em when I was working narco.
我们可以找到勒杜那个混蛋
We can get to that motherfucker Ledoux.
所以  别再来这套自我完善
So, enough with this self-improvement,
忏悔  绝望的把戏了
penance, hand-wringing shit.
干活儿吧
Let's go to work.
你觉得你
Do you think you're...
我操
Fuck!
你还真是会安慰病人啊  拉斯特
Hell of a bedside manner you got, Rust.
蠢和病是两回事
Ah, you know being stupid's different than callin' in sick,
而且这是酒吧  也不是病床
and this is a bar, not a fuckin' bedside.
患难见真情
Friend in need.
每次我以为你已经到顶的时候
Every time I think you hit a ceiling,
你都会蹦的更高
you just keep raising the bar.
你就像个混球版迈克尔·乔丹
You are like the Michael Jordan of being a son of a bitch.
走吧  你会喜欢我弄到的东西的
Let's go. Come on. Really gonna love this jacket I got.
我勒个去
Holy shit.
你常去看枪械展吗
You visit a lot of gun shows?
我存着这些枪
Ah, it's just some stuff
是为了防止过去惹的麻烦找上门来
I kept in case some work came back on me.
那些跟勒杜做交易的人
These boys Ledoux deals to,
是从德州东部来的
they're out of east Texas.
我当缉毒警的时候跟他们一起干过
I worked 'em when I was DEA task force.
他们知道你是警察吗
They know you're 5-0?
不知道
No.
我不确定
I wasn't sure,
所以我问了以前的联络人
so I checked with my old handler.
我在卧底的时候
As far as my cover goes,
在休斯敦一个港口的缉毒枪战中中了三枪
I took 3 slugs in a DEA shootout in port Houston.
所有人都以为我死了
Anybody that gives a shit figures I'm dead.
市长说过
Major said
缉毒队曾经管你叫克拉什
the task force used to call you Crash.
我需要一些私人时间
I'm gonna have to take some personal time
小马  大概几周
on this, Marty, a couple of weeks.
需要出去  找人打探  找找线索
Got to get out there and get seen, drop some lines.
警徽帮不了我们
I mean, badges ain't gonna get us near these people,
所以计划是我们给他们点甜头
so the plan is we make 'em an offer...
弄清楚他们的供货商
we get a line on their supplier,
确定就是勒杜
confirm it's Ledoux,
抓住他
bring him in.
我们在做这些事的时候
And then, once we're out there,
只能是我们两个人
all right, it's just you and me on this.
我不喜欢这样
I don't like that.
如果他们发现你的真实身份呢
What happens, they clock you're not you?
不行  如果有人看着就做不了我要做的了
No, I can't do what I need to do if we got watchdogs.
而且就像你说的  柯萨达会拖我后腿
Besides, like you said, Quesada'd pull me.
反正风险也没有那么高
The stakes ain't that high anyway.
被发现了不过一枪爆头而已
I get found, I take a bullet to the head.
有个我以前在边境卧底的贩毒集团
This cartel I worked on the border,
他们有个传统
they, uh, they had this routine.
会用胶带把你绑在一个固定在地上的椅子上
They'd duct-tape you to a chair that was bolted to the floor,
缠好几道
use a couple rolls,
确定你一点都动不了
make sure you couldn't budge a fuckin' inch.
然后他们会绕着你的脸切
And they'd cut around your face,
抓住你的头皮  猛的拉下来
grip your scalp, yank down,
把你整个脸都撕下来
rip your face off.
然后在你面前放一面镜子
And they'd put a mirror in front of you
让你好好看看自己什么样
so you could get a good look at yourself.
然后切下你的鸡巴和蛋
And they'd cut your dick and your balls off...
塞进嘴里  直到你血流不止  噎死为止
shove 'em down your throat until you bled and choked out,
还让你看着
while you were watching.
所以
So...
就高风险而言
as far as high stakes go,
一枪爆头
bullet to the head?
弱爆了
It ain't that.
你确定你要这样做吗
You sure you want to do this?
不确定
Not exactly.
你知道你这里有二楼的吧
Realize you got a upstairs here, right?
这是什么
What is that?
墨水和辣椒素
Ink and cayenne.
让皮肤发炎  看着像挫伤
Irritates the skin, looks contused.
他们让你在边境做了多久
How long they have you out there, working the corridor?
差不多四年
Almost 4 years.
四年  搞什么鬼
4? What the hell?
卧底们不应该工作超过11个月
UCs ain't supposed to do more than 11 months.
是啊  但是我把任务搞砸了
Yeah, but I--I'd fucked up on the job,
为了挽救局势  他们和我一起去了
and to make it better, they went with me.
那样的话  很难熬吧
That's a long time, being like that.
我需要个快速交易的借口  现在有了
I need a good story to move fast, and I think I got one.
现在只需要一些可卡因了
All we need now is some good coke.
你打算去哪儿搞
Where you gonna get that?
这你就别担心了
Don't worry about it.
所以你们找到了一个嫌疑人
So you got a suspect,
然后请了假
and youu take a leave of absence?
是的
Yup.
就像我说的  去见我老爸
Like I said, to see my pops.
他得了白血病
Had leukemia.
法夫尔  我来拿证据室的钥匙
Favre. Ahem. I get the evidence key from you?
不是说不着急吗
Yeah. Heard you were taking time.
谢谢  今晚就走
Thank you. Leaving tonight.
-别忘登记  -好的
- Sign the log. - Yep.
这个应该能看到两只眼睛吗
You supposed to see both eyes in this one?
他们真应该把系统搞好点
They really should have a better system for this.
我们看了你老搭档的档案
We looked at your old partner's history.
巧合不断  警探
And coincidences keep mounting, detective.
什么样的巧合
Oh, coincidences like what?
我不确定算不算是巧合  不过
Well, I don't know if it would qualify as coincidence, but,
就我们所知  他爸爸从来没得过白血病
near as we could tell, his pops never had leukemia.
没有任何医院记录
No hospital records of that.
事实上  30年以来  阿拉斯加那个镇上
Fact, nobody in that town in Alaska's
所有人都没见过特拉维斯·科尔
seen Travis Cohle in more than 30 years.
所以呢
That it?
你还在生你爸爸的气吗
You still angry at him, your pops?
不了
No.
他死了
He's dead.
但你当时很生气
You were, though.
不然你们两个为什么不说话了
I mean, why you two didn't talk.
我们从来没喜欢过对方
We never really liked each other.
这还是有区别的
There's a difference.
他去过越南
He was in 'nam.
休假的时候在加尔维斯顿遇到了我妈
Met my mother on leave in Galveston.
他回来的时候  我两岁
Time he came back, I was two.
她把我丢给了他
She dumped me on him,
然后拍屁股走人  我们两个搬到了阿拉斯加
then she hauled ass, and he and I moved to Alaska.
他是个幸存者  可以这么说
He was a survivalist, I guess you'd call it.
有过一些非常奇葩的想法
Had some very fucking strange ideas.
没有比那里静谧的夜空更美的事物了
Oh, there's nothing like the night sky out there, though.
但是我有点怕冷
But I couldn't handle the cold, so...
所以我回到了南德克萨斯  因为我记得
I headed back to South Texas 'cause all I could remember
那里至少不冷
was at least it never got cold.
我爸经常让我觉得我那么做让他失望了
My old man always made like I let him down that way.
说我毫无忠诚之心
Said I had no loyalty.
趁他们还小  一刀两断是最好的选择
A clean break is best now, while they're still young.
听着  那和我无关
Look, that's none of my business.
我想说的是我还需要他的协助
I mean, but I do need him to watch my back on this.
所以你们全都变得一团糟
This is how you all get warped.
你们总是低估自己的错误
You always short-change the wrong things.
低估
Short-change?
还有什么
What else?
他想让我道个歉  不过这就算了
He wanted me to pass a tide of apologies of which I'll skip...
他想见见女孩儿们
and he wants to see the girls,
如果你能安排一下的话
if you can make time for it.
孩子们是唯一重要的事  玛姬
Kids are the only thing that matter, Maggie.
男女间的这些事都是因为孩子
They're the only reason for this whole man-woman drama.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你到底在说什么
What are you suggesting, exactly?
人会把事情搞砸
Just that people fuck up.
我们会变老
We age.
男人和女人
Men, women,
除了繁衍后代外不应该发展其它关系
it's not supposed to work except to make kids.
如果你把小马的行为
So, if you can imagine
看作是软弱  痛苦的表现
Marty's behavior as an expression of weakness, pain,
你就能看出来那并不是因为你
you'd see that it's not about you.
到最后  你跟其他人一样
So, end of the day, you duck under rationalization,
拿合理化当挡箭牌
same as any of them.
你肯定是一个好丈夫
You must have been a great husband.
我露面有差不多一个星期了
People have been seeing me around for about a week.
我打过交道的那个人  今晚想和我见面
Guy I used to run with, he wants to meet me tonight.
如果我能让他落单
Now, if I can get him alone,
咱们把他抓起来
we snatch him up,
审讯一下  也许能发现勒杜的线索
work him over, maybe get to Ledoux.
向东  橘子郡
向西  博蒙特
-好吧  -好吗
- Ok. - All right?
很好
Great.
-听着  -电话已经充满电了
- Listen. - Phone's fully charged.
记住  用起来非常简单
And remember, it's real simple.
绿色的  接听  红色的  挂断
Green, answers, red, hangs up.
好的
All right.
我是唯一一个会打这个电话的人
I'm the only one that's gonna be calling.
-好的  -让它一直充着电
- Yeah. - And keep it charged.
听着  她怎么样
Listen, uh, how was she?
她说了什么
What'd she say?
她好些了  我能看出来她的态度在软化
She was better. I could see her softening.
她没用D打头的那个词
she didn't use the "D" Word.
我敢打赌  你们两个
My odds, I could see you
几个月之内肯定又能在一起了
two back together within a couple months.
你真的这么认为吗
That your honest read?
我真的这么认为  小马
That's my honest read, Marty.
听着  我不知道
Look, I don't know
我今晚要见的这个人对我有什么想法
how this guy I'm meeting tonight feels about me.
-记住了吗  -那是什么意思
- Ok? - What does that mean?
意思是  今晚如果你失去了我的踪迹
It means, if you lose track of me tonight,
拿着这该死的对讲机
keep this fucker handy
听博蒙特警方的频道
and be listening to Beaumont police channels.
-好的  -记住了吗
- Yeah. - You got it?
记住了
Yeah.
真的记住了吗
You got it?
真的  你会没事的对吧
I got it. Are you gonna be all right?
但愿
Yeah.
我是克拉什  来找金杰的
Crash, here for Ginger.
在休斯敦之后
Well, after Houston,
我去老鹰隘口找了一个医生
I got to a doc in Eagle Pass,
然后一个蛇头带我偷渡出境
Then a coyote got me across the border.
之后两年  我在圣米格尔
Past two years, I been working security
为一个小组做安保工作
for a group in San Miguel.
警察从来没抓到过我
Feds never ID'd me, you know,
所以我觉得
so I figured,
已经过了两年了  风头已过
hell, two years pass, things chill down,
我是时候回来了
It's cool for me to come back, stick my head up.
那很难  伙计
That'll be tough, man...
这么长时间以来一直以为你已经死了
Thinkin' you been dead this whole time.
我看起来像死了吗  混账东西
I look dead, motherfucker?
我想继续和你干
I'm lookin' to get with you.
你或者迈尔斯
You or Miles.
迈尔斯不想见到你  克拉什
Miles ain't gonna want to see you, Crash.
-我认为他会想的  -好吧
- Oh, I think he might. - Well, yeah.
那么我换个说法
Then I'd say
我不认为你想见到迈尔斯
I don't think you want to see Miles.
伙计  我不是来惹事的  好吗
Man, I ain't here to start a thing, all right?
我在墨西哥打交道的那帮人
Boys I been running with in Mexico,
愿意跟我们做笔大的
there could be a hell of a deal for both sides,
挣大笔的钱
Fuckin' money to be made.
真真正正的钱
Real money.
是什么行当
What kind of money?
该死的拉斯特
Goddamn Rust.
我操他妈
What the fuck?
我的人已经准备好交易了
My boys are looking to trade, all right?
可卡因换冰毒
Coke for meth.
你拿的是什么
What you got there?
-专门给你准备的  -专门给我的
- This one's just for you. - Just for me?
你兑了什么
What'd you cut it with?
你会知道的
Oh, you'll see.
你自己尝
You'll dig it.
说来还是不信任我啊
After all I meant to you, huh?
那些人究竟是谁
Now, who exactly are these guys?
他  他们
Uh, they, uh...
墨西哥军方出来的
Ex-mex army.
跟哥伦比亚那边有关系
They got a Colombian connection.
他们在边境的加工厂需要冰毒
They need meth for the maquiladoras.
他们也可以自己生产
Yeah, they could cook it themselves,
可这样会被其他毒贩发现
but then the cartels would take notice,
他们不希望那样
and that ain't what they're lookin' for.
给
Here.
尝尝这个  兄弟
Taste that, homie.
真他妈纯
That ain't no fuck-around shit.
我操
Goddamn.
你留着吧
You keep it.
这东西我那儿多的是
I've got bulldozers' worth of that shit where I came from.
问题是
The thing is...
我们有人帮我们制毒
We got one cook.
基本把活全包了
Does all our work, exclusive-like.
而且活干得非常好
He's real specific about that.
你想我做什么  克拉什  卖给迈尔斯吗
Now, what's this worth to you, Crash, me selling Miles on this?
我有个更好的提议  兄弟
Well, I'd got you one better, brother.
我们根本不给迈尔斯
We don't take that shit to Miles at all.
我们自己做供货商
You and me work the supplier,
愿意抽多少都行
the cut's whatever the fuck we want it to be.
这可他妈的不容易  兄弟
Now, now, that's tricky shit, bro,
我跟你没以前那么熟了
and I don't know you like I used to.
我跟你也没以前那么熟
Yeah, I don't know you like I used to, either.
这就是他妈的为什么我要过来
That's why the fuck I'm here.
我来告诉你为什么我会来  克拉什
Well, let me tell you why I came, Crash.
我今晚需要你做点事
I need something from you, tonight.
我手下有四个人要干一票大的
I had a 4-man team for a big grab,
其中一个被抓了
lost one to smokies.
我要找人替他
I came looking to replace him,
如果你还干这行的话
if you're still a bad-ass.
我烧杀掳掠  也不抢银行
I don't do A and R, man, no fuckin' bank jobs.
不是那种事
It ain't nothin' like that.
我需要一个听话的
I need a good soldier.
跟我们干这票
Now, you do this with us,
我就帮你牵线
we talk about puttin' you with my man.
听着
Look.
我不当牛仔很多年了  金杰
I don't ride cowboy no more, Ginger.
我不做你说的这种
Oh. I don't do this small-time shit
屁大的事了
like this thing you're talking about, all right?
你他妈在南部让人阉了吧
What, you get neutered down south, huh?
我很享受这法外的生活
I embrace the outlaw life.
你还穿着这身呢
Now, you dress the part still.
还是说你在演戏
That just an act?
也许是吧
When in rome, brother,
不过我很会收拾残局
but I do clean up real fuckin' pretty.
操他娘的  我需要个神枪手
Motherfucker, I need a gunslinger.
别那么胆小了  跟我干吧
Now, you ain't too timid, get on this shit with me.
这样才好谈合作
Then we can talk about doin' business.
在哪
Where?
我那儿
My place.
河口下面
Down the bayou.
好吧  我开车过去
All right. I got my truck.
这里很安全
It'll be safe here.
仅限会员
Members only.
我来找我朋友
I'm just lookin' for a friend.
你他妈的干嘛
Hey. What the fuck?
听我说  我朋友不在这里
Look, look, look, my buddy's not here.
-你没听到吗  -我是他的监护人
- You ain't listening! - I'm his sponsor, and
我担心他又开始酗酒了
I'm worried that he might have started drinking again.
你应该担心我们会不会把你脑袋揪下来
You better worry that we don't pull your head off
往你脖子里拉屎
and shit down your neck!
他戒酒二十年了
He's been 20 years sober.
让我看一眼就好
Just give me one second.
这他妈怎么回事
What the hell!
-我马上就走  -居然有人进来
- I'm leaving, Sir. - A guy can just come in here and say,
说他娘的什么"找朋友"
"Lookin' for a fuckin' friend"?!
管好你自己的蛋吧  娘炮
Ought to worry more about your balls, faggot!
给我他娘的滚出去
Get the fuck outta here!
我就走
I'm leaving.
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
快滚  操你妈的
Run, motherfucker!
很不错
That's good.
去你妈的
Son of a bitch, man!
那边怎么了
Fuck is that? That there?
是黑鬼泰格  本名叫泰格·托马斯
That's Tigger the Nigger. Name's Tiger Thomas.
霍斯顿那片的毒贩子  你认识他们吗
Dealer in them Hoston projects. You know them?
他们住在那一片平房里  是吧
That's like them bungalowed, flat-like joints, right?
没错
Yeah.
他们在那里有个仓库
They keep a stash house there.
我会逮到你们的  你们这帮混蛋
I'll get you, you fucking dicks!
他妈的闭嘴吧  你个黑鬼
Hey, why don't you shut the fuck up, Nigger?
去你妈的
Fuck you!
你们就打算靠四个人
So you all gonna take a stash house
围攻一处仓库是吗
in coon country, huh, 4 guys?
那边的楼群有多大  一块街区那么大吗
Well, how big's the projects, man, like square block-wise?
去拿装备  伙计
Get the gear, mates.
给你看看这个  你肯定喜欢
Wait till you see this. You're gonna love it.
你们想装成警察混进去
Oh, you're going in as cops, huh?
没错
Uh-huh. Yeah.
你知道仓库在哪吗
You know where the stash house is?
泰格带我们过去
Tiger's gonna take us there.
那你有撤退计划吗
Well, you got an exit plan?
时间安排
Timetable?
要是真的警察来了  该怎么办
The real cops come, then what, huh?
你们就开一辆车进去吗
I mean, you say you're going in the one fuckin' car?
我没记错的话
Far as I remember, man,
那地方是条死路
the place is blocked in.
只有一条路可以进出
That is one way in, one way out.
跟个鬼城似的
It could be fuckin' Mogadishu, man.
要是遇到麻烦
We hit trouble,
就只能硬着头皮上
you're just gonna fuck it in the ass.
爆头杀人  毫不手软
You scoop out the soft brains inside the skull.
看来你想得很周全
Well, so you have thought it out.
是我小瞧你们了
My bad.
向东  橘子郡
向西  博蒙特
我帮你搞定今晚
I come through for you on this tonight,
你得保证帮我联系
I got to know you're gonna hook me up,
我可有正经活要干
'cause I got a real job I was supposed to be doing.
我保证  你帮我搞定这个活  我就帮你
You got my word. You back me on this, I'll back you.
操  走吧
Fuck it. Let's go.
该起床了  软茄子
Up and at 'em, eggplant.
一帮混蛋
Motherfuckers.
-去你妈的  -走吧
- Fuck you! - Come on.
你们死定了  死定了
Y'all are dead! Y'all are dead!
富林顿大街发生盗窃案
406 reported on Fullington street...
调度台  这里是空勤三号
Air 3, dispatch.
请说  空勤三号
Go ahead, Air 3.
到达六号霍斯顿楼群区域
Over zone 6, Hoston projects.
很安静  应该只是妨碍公务
Pretty quiet, possible 507s.
不需出警
Everything's code 4.
收到  空勤三号  收到
Copy that. 10-4, Air 3.
这件事可以从两方面考虑  泰格
Man, you got two ways of lookin' at it, Tiger.
你可以死  失去一切
You can die and lose your shit,
也可以活下来
or you could live,
接着烧杀抢夺
go make some more shit.
-怎么了  -立刻进屋  我们是警察
- What's up? - Y'all get back in your house, now. Police.
警察  回屋去  快点
Sheriff's department! Get back in your house. Do it.
这没什么可看的
There's nothin' to see here.
你个混蛋
Sorry son of a bitch.
-滚出来带路  -操  快点
- Fuck out of here and start going... - Fucker, start moving.
嘿  泰格  怎么了  什么情况
Tiger, man, yo. What's up, man? What's this?
-操  拉马尔  -警察
- Yo! Fuck! Lamar! - Sheriff's department.
-拉马尔  -不许动  混蛋
- Lamar! - Freeze, motherfucker.
过来  大个子  敲门
Get up there, big boy. Get on the door.
-告诉他们很安全  -拉马尔
- Tell them that it's safe. - Lamar.
-放开我  -开门  拉马尔
- Get the fuck off me! - Come open the door, Lamar.
-说你是谁  -他妈的开门  我是泰格
- Tell them who you are. - Fuckin' door, man. It's tiger.
过来  退后  警察
Get up here. Get back! police!
操
Fuck!
所有人跪下  快点
Everybody down, now!
警察  双手放在脑后
Sheriffs! Hands behind your head!
闭嘴  快他妈的跪下
Shut up! Get the fuck down!
不许动
Don't move.
躲到浴缸里去
Get in the tub.
听着  趴低点  千万别动
Listen, listen. You lay down. Don't you move.
这啥也没有  放我走
Got no shit! Let me outta here!
他妈的闭嘴
Shut your fuckin' mouth!
去左边翻翻  肯定就在这
Look on the left. It's right there.
不  不  不  金杰  别碰
No, no, no, no. Ginger, no. Don't touch it.
-就在这  -你来打开  混蛋
- It's in there. - You open it, motherfucker.
别拿枪指着我
Get that gun out of my face.
再不闭嘴我就一枪崩了你
I'll put something else In your face, you don't shut up.
快点滚过去  快点
Get your fuckin' ass over there! Start movin'!
快点
Come on!
金杰
Ginger.
你个混蛋  把它关了
You motherfucker! Get that shit off of there!
-快点  你他妈快点  -操
- Come on! Hurry your ass up! - Fuck.
操
Fuck you!
30秒  拿了就走
All right, 30 seconds, in and out.
30秒  拿了就走  金杰
30 seconds, in and out, Ginger.
快把保险箱打开
Get that safe open.
小心点  小心点  我会搞死你的  混蛋
Watch it, watch it. I'll nuke you, motherfucker.
把嘴闭上
Keep your fuckin' mouth shut.
老子一枪崩了你  混蛋
I'm gonna fire on you, motherfucker.
别碰我的热
Get the fuck off my dawg!
放轻松  放轻松
Easy, easy.
拿上货就走  金杰
Just get in and get the fuck out, Ginger.
过节了  克拉什  到手了
It's christmastime, Crash! We got this shit!
放轻松
Easy.
冷静  快点  金杰  该走了
Stay calm. Get it, Ginger. Get the fuck out of here.
金杰  他们的人都聚在外面了
Ginger, man, they're gathering out there--
快点  金杰
Come on, Ginger!
他们可不好惹
They're animals out there, man.
放轻松  混蛋
Easy, motherfucker.
放轻松  放轻松
Easy. Easy.
金杰  该走了
Ginger, let's fuckin' go!
你个可悲的混蛋
You sorry-ass motherfucker!
我说过  你们死定了
I told your cracker ass! You're dead!
别开枪  别
Don't fucking fire! Do not--
干
Goddamn it.
拉马尔
Lamar!
金杰  金杰  你他妈快点
Ginger! Ginger! Stop fuckin' around!
操
Fuck!
操  金杰
What the fuck! Ginger!
我就知道
I fuckin' knew it!
一开始就该这么干的  你个白痴
Wish I could have done this from the start, you fucking moron!
操  你他妈干什么
Oh, fuck! What the fuck are you doin', man?
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
混蛋
Motherfucker!
不许动  还有是会在屋里
Freeze. Who else is in the house?
-没人  -到厕所里去
- Nobody. - Ok. Get in the bathroom.
进厕所  趴下
In the bathroom. Lay down.
小马
Marty, ok.
我要你一分半之后到18和19大街
I need you to meet me at Amelia street
中间的阿梅利亚街来接我
between 18th and 19th in 90 seconds.
记住了吗  记住了吗
You got it? You got it?
阿梅利亚
Amelia!
18和19大街
18th and 19th!
一分半  混蛋
90 seconds, motherfucker!
那里有一个
Ooh, one right there!
又来一个
Here comes another one!
起来  来啊
Get your ass up! Come on!
金杰
Ginger.
你个白痴
You stupid mother--
整个街区都
The neighborhood--
快点  警察在后面
Come on, man! Police behind us, man!
快点
Come on.
快走  快点
Keep going, man! Come on! Hurry up, man!
放下武器
Put the weapon down!
你个混蛋
You motherfucker!
我会收拾你的
I'll get you!
你会被收拾的  混蛋克拉什
You'll get yours, fuckin' Crash, you motherfucker.
你会被收拾
You'll get--aah!
举起双手走出来
Come out with your hands raised!
跪下
Get down on your knees!
快点  藏起来  这里
Quick, hide. Here.
干
Oh, shit!
走  走
Go! Go.
走  走  走
Go, go, go!
怎么回事
What the fuck happened?
现在想起来联络人是谁了没
Remember that meth contact now?
你个叛徒  混蛋
You rat motherfucker!
告诉我勒杜在哪里
You're gonna give me the location for Ledoux,
我就放过你  金杰
I'm gonna let you slide, Ginger.
草泥马
Bullshit.
不然你以为我找你干什么
What the fuck you think I want with you, huh?
操  我都不想跟你说话了
Oh, goddamn. I am so done talking to you like a man.
继续开
Go, go.